On the 19th June, 2016, during a Sunday Live Service at The SCOAN, Prophet T.B. Joshua gave a prophecy
and a call to pray for the nation, the United Kingdom
These were his words.
We were all here when I said, "Pray for the United Kingdom"
and I said I’m seeing a strange thing happen -
it will happen to an innocent person.
It is not yet over.
They should pray and make sure they secure their lawmakers and their institution.
Let me put it that way.
Because this institution, they are the ministers and all other that make up the body
to support the president at the top.
Institution – they should give proper security to their institution in the United Kingdom.
Rise up for prayer.
RV: Mel Flowers 25/03/2019